Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Committee files
  - Rules
    - H Res 168 est. corrections calendar (Box 400, Folder 11)
      Democratic whip flyer, CR. Includes: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 168 establishing a corrections calendar. 1995 Jun 20. [13] l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections
    - H Res 173 (HJ Res 79 flag amendment) (Box 400, Folder 12)
      ACB managed; passed (Democrats opposed / closed). Democratic minority whip flyer, correspondence, analysis, CR, CRS report, clippings. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 173 rule for HJ Res 79 proposing an amendment to the Constitution on flag desecration. 15 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 176 (HR 1944 appropriations) (Box 400, Folder 13)
      ACB managed. Copy, CR. Also: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 176 providing for consideration of HR 1944 emergency supplemental appropriations and rescissions for FY 95. 6 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 180 (Select CR HR 483) (Box 400, Folder 14)
      ACB managed. Memo, copy, CR. Also: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 180 HR 483 Medicare Select Expansion. 5 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 171 (HR 1905 energy) (Box 401, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, memos, analysis, copy, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 171 rule for HR 1905 energy and water appropriations FY 1996. 1995 Jul 11. [4] l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections
    - H Res 185, 187, 189 (HR 1977 Interior) (Box 401, Folder 2)
      ACB managed. For Jul 12 - 13, 17. Copy of resolution, CR. Also: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 189, the rule providing for further consideration of HR 1977 Interior appropriations for FY 96. 1995 Jul 17. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 190 (HR 2020 Treasury) (Box 401, Folder 3)
      ACB managed. Passed voice. Correspondence, analysis. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for HR 2020, Treasure, Postal Service appropriations, fiscal year 1996. 1995 Jul 18. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections. Also 2 additional l (FAX)
    - H Res rule for S 395 (oil export) (Box 401, Folder 4)
      Dissenting views, statements. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for conference report on S 395 lifting the ban on Alaskan crude oil exports. 1995 Nov 8. 4 l. Typescript (printer)
    - H Res 194 (HR 2002 Transportation) (Box 401, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, amendments, analysis, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 194 rule for HR 2002, FY 1996 appropriations bill for transportation and related agencies. 1995 Jul 21. 12 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections
    - H Res 201 (HR 2099 VA and HUD) (Box 401, Folder 6)
      ACB managed. CR. Also: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res [201] providing for consideration of HR 2099 VA - HUD - independent agencies appropriations for FY 96. 1995 Jul 27. 11 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 204 (S 21 Bosnia) (Box 401, Folder 7)
      ACB managed. Analysis, statements, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 204 rule for consideration of S 21 terminating U.S. arms embargo on Bosnia. 1995 Aug 1. 11 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections
    - Rule on HR 1555 (telecom reform) (Box 401, Folder 8)
      ACB managed. Correspondence, analysis, CR
    - H Res 216 (HR 1655 intelligence) (Box 401, Folder 9)
      ACB managed. Correspondence, copies. Also: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for HR 1655, 1996 Intelligence Authorization Act. 1995 Sep 12. 11 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 219 (HR 1670 Federal acq) (Box 401, Folder 10)
      ACB managed. Copy, analysis. Also: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 219 providing for consideration of HR 1670 Federal Acquisition Reform Act of 1995. 1995 Sep 13. 5 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 225 (HR 927 Cuba) (Box 401, Folder 11)
      ACB handled (no). Correspondence, analysis, statements, clipping. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for consideration of HR 927 Cuban Liberty and Democratic Solidarity Act. 1995 Sep 20. 7 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with extensive holograph corrections
    - Conference on HR 1530 (Defense Elk Hills) (Box 401, Folder 12)
      Correspondence, memos, CR
    - H Res 231 (CR on HR 1977 Interior) (Box 401, Folder 13)
      CR, statement: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 231 providing for consideration of the conference report on HR 1977 Interior appropriations for FY 964. 1995 Sep 28. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 227 (HR 1170 courts) (Box 401, Folder 14)
      ACB managed, passed voice. Correspondence, analysis, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 227 rule for HR 1170, three - judge courts. 1995 Sep 27. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 234 (HR 2405 civilian science) (Box 401, Folder 15)
      ACB managed, passed voice. Correspondence, analysis, copy. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 234 rule for HR 2405, Omnibus Civilian Science Authorization Act of 1995. 1995 Oct 10. [7] l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 241 (HR 2002 Transportation) (Box 401, Folder 16)
      ACB managed. Copy, CR only
    - H Res 245 (HR 2491 budget) (Box 401, Folder 17)
      ACB managed. Copy, CR, statement: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 245 providing for consideration of HR 2491 budget reconciliation for 1996 - 2002. 1995 Oct 26. 3 l. Typescript (printer)
    - H Res 248 (HR 1905 energy) (Box 401, Folder 18)
      ACB managed. Copy, analysis, CR, statement: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for conference report on HR 1905 energy and water appropriations. 1995 Oct 31. 4 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res for HR 1833 (abortion) (Box 402, Folder 1)
      ACB managed, passed 241 - 181. Correspondence, testimony, copy, analysis. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for HR 1833 "Partial - Birth Abortion Ban Act." 1995 Nov 1. 8 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 257 (appropriations) (Box 402, Folder 2)
      ACB managed, passed. Analysis, Democratic whip flyer, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for HJ Res 115, further continuing appropriations for fiscal year 1996. 1995 Nov 8. 10 l. Typescript (large font, printer). Deals with limiting non profits spending for advocacy
    - H Res 261 (HJ Res 115 appropriations) (Box 402, Folder 3)
      ACB handled. Correspondence, CR, clipping. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 261 rule for HJ Res 115, further continuing appropriations for fiscal year 1996. 1995 Nov 10. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 265 (two thirds waiver) (Box 402, Folder 4)
      Voice passage. Correspondence, copy, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 261 rule for HJ Res 115, further continuing appropriations for fiscal year 1996. 1995 Nov 10. 8 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - H Res 253 (Interior appropriations) (Box 402, Folder 5)
      CR, statement: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 253 providing for consideration of the conference report on HR 1977 Interior appropriations for FY 96. 1995 Nov 15. 12 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections
    - H Res 267 (CR on HR 2020 Treasury) (Box 402, Folder 6)
      Memos, Democratic whip flyer, amendments. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution rule for conference report on HR 202 Treasury / Postal appropriations. 1995 Nov 15. 9 l. Typescript (large font, printer). Also copy in regular font
    - H Res 272 (CR on budget) (Box 402, Folder 7)
      Copy, CR, statement: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on H Res 272 providing for consideration of conference report on HR 2491, seven - year budget reconciliation act. 3 l. Typescript ( printer)
    - H Res 276 (waive two thirds) (Box 402, Folder 8)
      CR, statement: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 276 waiving two thirds rule. 6 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 291 (CR on VA / HUD) (Box 402, Folder 9)
      ACB managed, passed. Correspondence, analysis
    - H Res 301 (Interior appropriations) (Box 402, Folder 10)
      Copy, CR, statement: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution providing for consideration of the conference report on HR 1977 Interior appropriations for FY 96. 1995 Dec 13. 12 l. Typescript (large font, printer). With 4 l. talking points on rejecting the Tongass rider
    - H Res 313 (HR 558 Texas waste) (Box 402, Folder 11)
      ACB managed. Passed / voice. Correspondence, analysis, copy, CR. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 313 rule for HR 558 Texas waste compact. 1995 Dec 20. [3] l. Typescript (large font, printer) with minor holograph corrections
    - H Res 318 (HR 1655 intelligence) (Box 402, Folder 12)
      ACB managed. Correspondence, analysis, CR, statements. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on House Resolution 318 rule for conference report or HR 1655 1996 Intelligence Authorization Act. 1995 Dec 21. 12 l. Typescript (large font, printer) with holograph corrections. Note posted on manuscript: Cross praised ACB statement - "excellent," "compelling"
    - HR 1158 / 1944 (Box 402, Folder 13)
      Earthquake bills. Correspondence, copies of bills, etc
  - Task Force on Immigration
    - Business for the dates noted (Box 390, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, clippings. Includes: Concurring and dissenting remarks of Hon.. Anthony C. Beilenson, Hon. Howard L. Berman, and Hon. Jane Harman. No date. 3 l. Typescript (printer copy)
- Constituent services
  - Correspondence
    - Incoming / outgoing
      - Sepulveda Basin - 23rd CD (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - Sepulveda Basin - 23rd CD (Box 377, Folder 7)
      - Sepulveda Basin - 23rd CD (Box 377, Folder 8)
      - Sepulveda Basin - 24th CD (Box 377, Folder 9)
  - District
    - Los Angeles rail. f.1 of 2 (Box 387, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, memos, statements, clippings. Includes: Statement of Hon Anthony C. Beilenson before the Subcommittee on Transportation Committee on Appropriations. 1991 May 1. 2 l. Typescript (photocopy)
    - Los Angeles rail. f.2 of 2 (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - Point Mugu. f.1 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      Statement, news releases. Includes: statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson Member of Congress, 24th district, California, Testimony before the Base Realignment and Closure Commission, Washington D.C. hearing. 1995 Jun 12. 2 l. Typescript (large font, printer) and list of expected questions. Also press releases: Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson ... on status of Point Mugu. 1995 May 10. Congressman Beilenson: Navy is committed to saving Point Mugu. 1995 May 17. Point Mugu's status should not be determined by 1993 figures, Defense Department Inspector General tells Congressman Beilenson. Congressman Beilenson testifies before Base Closure Commission on saving Point Mugu. 1995 Jun 12. Statement of Congressman Anthony C. Beilenson ... on BRAC Commission decision to save Point Mugu. 1995 Jun 22
    - Point Mugu. f.2 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - Point Mugu. f.3 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 5)
    - Point Mugu. f.4 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 6)
    - Point Mugu. f.5 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles rail / San Fernando Valley. f.1 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 8)
      News release: Beilenson announces support for Burbank - Chandler subway. 1992 Aug 14
    - Los Angeles rail / San Fernando Valley. f.2 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles rail / San Fernando Valley. f.3 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles rail / San Fernando Valley. f.4 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles rail / San Fernando Valley. f.5 of 5 (Box 387, Folder 12)
    - Earthquake EDA. For the dates noted (Box 388, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, statements. Includes: Congressmen Beilenson, Berman, and Dixon announce EDA planning grant for Los Angeles County. 1994 May 27. Congressman Beilenson announces release of $30 million disaster assistance to help businesses. 1994 Jun 23
    - Earthquake meeting (Box 388, Folder 2)
      Report, memos, clippings
    - Earthquake EDA. For the date noted (Box 388, Folder 3)
      Memos, statement. Includes: Statement of Hon. Anthony C. Beilenson on release of Earthquake Disaster Assistance Funds. 1994 Jun 23. 3 l. Typescript (large font, printer)
    - Earthquake. For the dates noted (Box 388, Folder 4)
    - Earthquake. For the dates noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 388, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, memos, reports
    - Earthquake. For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 388, Folder 6)
      Clippings (newsprint
    - Earthquake. Ventura County (Box 388, Folder 7)
    - Earthquake (HUD) (Box 388, Folder 8)
    - Earthquake (SBA) (Box 388, Folder 9)
      SBA: Small Business Administration
  - Issue mail
    - Outgoing (carbon or photocopies)
      - Academies (Box 178, Folder 1)
        Material in this series filed in looseleaf binders, transferred to folders labeled with binder headings. Some headings had no material filed after them and is so noted
      - ACB legis: SMMNRA (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - ACB legis: Elephants (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - ACB legis: Autos (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - ACB legis: other (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Agriculture (Box 178, Folder 6)
      - Applications: ACB staff (Box 178, Folder 7)
        Also includes Academies applications
      - Applications: Interns (Box 178, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations [no documents filed] (Box 178, Folder 9)
      - Arts & humanities (Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Beilenson: general (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - Beilenson: recommendations (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - Beilenson: congratulations (Box 178, Folder 13)
      - Budget: general (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - California: general (Box 178, Folder 15)
      - California: LA Metrorail (Box 178, Folder 16)
      - Commerce: general (Box 178, Folder 17)
      - Commerce: banking (Box 178, Folder 18)
      - Unfiled items (Box 178, Folder 19)
      - Communications: general (Box 178, Folder 20)
      - Communications: AT&T (Box 178, Folder 21)
      - Congress (Box 178, Folder 22)
      - CR inserts (Box 178, Folder 23)
      - Consumer affairs (Box 178, Folder 24)
      - Defense: armed services (Box 178, Folder 25)
      - Defense: general (Box 178, Folder 26)
      - Defense: weapons (Box 178, Folder 27)
      - Economy (Box 178, Folder 28)
      - Education (Box 178, Folder 29)
      - Energy: conservation, alternative (Box 178, Folder 30)
      - Energy: general (Box 178, Folder 31)
      - Energy: gas oil coal (Box 178, Folder 32)
      - Energy: nuclear (Box 178, Folder 33)
      - Unfiled [primarily APHIS] (Box 178, Folder 34)
      - Environment: animals (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Environment: general (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Environment: parks (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Environment: pollution (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Federal government: civil service (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Federal government: general (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Health: general (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Health: Medicare (Box 179, Folder 8)
      - Health: food and drugs (Box 179, Folder 9)
      - Health: tobacco (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Health: insurance (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Housing (Box 179, Folder 12)
      - Human services: general (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Human services: Social Security (Box 179, Folder 14)
        Ends binder
      - International relations: general (Box 179, Folder 15)
        Begins binder
      - International relations: Central America (Box 179, Folder 16)
      - International relations: Middle East (Box 179, Folder 17)
      - International relations: human rights (Box 179, Folder 18)
      - International relations: trade (Box 179, Folder 19)
      - International relations: world hunger (Box 179, Folder 20)
      - Judiciary: abortion (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Judiciary: bankruptcy (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Judiciary: busing (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Judiciary: civil rights (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Judiciary: crime (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Judiciary: general (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Judiciary: gun control (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Judiciary: immigration (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Unfiled (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Labor: general (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Labor: pensions / wages (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous mail: general (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous mail: newsletters (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Office administration (Box 180, Folder 14)
      - Political: general / national (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - Political: election reform (Box 180, Folder 16)
      - Postal service (Box 180, Folder 17)
      - Public works (Box 180, Folder 18)
      - Request (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - Science and technology (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Taxation: general (Box 180, Folder 21)
      - Taxation: reforms (Box 180, Folder 22)
      - Tax: personal (Box 180, Folder 23)
      - Tax: business (Box 180, Folder 24)
      - Tax: invest / savings (Box 180, Folder 25)
      - Transportation: general (Box 180, Folder 26)
      - Transportation: air (Box 180, Folder 27)
      - Transportation: rail / Amtrak (Box 180, Folder 28)
      - Veterans Affairs (Box 180, Folder 29)
      - Visitors (Box 180, Folder 30)
        End binder
      - Filing key (Box 180, Folder 31)
      - ACB dictated (Box 180, Folder 32)
        Begin binder
      - Printed forms [sample form letters] (Box 180, Folder 33)
      - Agriculture (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations: general [empty when transferred] (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Arts and humanities: general (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Beilenson: personal (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Budget: general (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - California: general (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - California: 23rd and Los Angeles (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - Commerce: general (Box 181, Folder 8)
      - Commerce: banking (Box 181, Folder 9)
      - Communications: general (Box 181, Folder 10)
      - Communications: phone (Box 181, Folder 11)
      - Congress: general (Box 181, Folder 12)
      - Consumer protection: general (Box 181, Folder 13)
      - Defense and national security: general (Box 181, Folder 14)
      - Defense: Armed Services (Box 181, Folder 15)
      - Defense: Intelligence / National Security (Box 181, Folder 16)
      - Defense: spending (Box 181, Folder 17)
      - Defense: weapons (Box 181, Folder 18)
      - Defense: weapons, nuclear (Box 181, Folder 19)
      - Defense: weapons, SDI (Box 181, Folder 20)
      - District of Columbia (Box 181, Folder 21)
      - Education: general (Box 181, Folder 22)
      - Energy: general (Box 181, Folder 23)
      - Energy and fuels: conservation (Box 181, Folder 24)
      - Energy and fuels: gas oil (Box 181, Folder 25)
      - Energy and fuels: nuclear energy (Box 181, Folder 26)
      - Environment: general (Box 181, Folder 27)
      - Environment: animals (Box 181, Folder 28)
      - Environment: parks (Box 181, Folder 29)
      - Environment: pollution (Box 181, Folder 30)
      - Federal government: general (Box 181, Folder 31)
      - Federal government: Civil Service (Box 181, Folder 32)
      - Health: general (Box 181, Folder 33)
      - Health: diseases (Box 181, Folder 34)
      - Health: AIDS (Box 181, Folder 35)
      - Health: food drugs alcohol (Box 181, Folder 36)
      - Health: insurance / health care costs (Box 181, Folder 37)
      - Health: Medicaid / Medicare (Box 181, Folder 38)
      - Health: smoking (Box 181, Folder 39)
      - Housing and Community Development: general (Box 181, Folder 40)
      - Human services: general (Box 181, Folder 41)
      - Human services: Social Security (Box 181, Folder 42)
      - Human services: Social Security - Notch (Box 181, Folder 43)
      - Human services: Welfare and SSI [empty when transferred] (Box 181, Folder 44)
      - Academies (Box 181, Folder 45)
      - ACB legislation (Box 181, Folder 46)
      - Agriculture (Box 181, Folder 47)
      - Applications: ACB staff (Box 181, Folder 48)
        Also general applications
      - Applications: interns (Box 181, Folder 49)
      - Appropriations (Box 181, Folder 50)
      - Arts and humanities (Box 181, Folder 51)
      - Beilenson (Box 181, Folder 52)
      - Budget (Box 181, Folder 53)
      - California: general (Box 181, Folder 54)
      - California: Metrorail (Box 181, Folder 55)
      - Commerce: general (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Commerce: banking (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Communications: general (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Communications: phone (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Congress (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Consumer affairs (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Defense: general (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Defense: Armed Services (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - Defense: Intelligence (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - Defense: spending (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - Defense: weapons (Box 182, Folder 11)
      - District of Columbia (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - Economy: general (Box 182, Folder 13)
      - Education (Box 182, Folder 14)
      - Energy: general (Box 182, Folder 15)
      - Energy: conservation (Box 182, Folder 16)
      - Energy: gas oil (Box 182, Folder 17)
      - Energy: nuclear (Box 182, Folder 18)
      - Environment: general (Box 182, Folder 19)
      - Environment: animals (Box 182, Folder 20)
      - Environment: parks (Box 182, Folder 21)
      - Environment: pollution (Box 182, Folder 22)
      - Federal government: general (Box 182, Folder 23)
      - Federal government: Civil Service (Box 182, Folder 24)
      - Health: general (Box 182, Folder 25)
      - Health: diseases (Box 182, Folder 26)
      - Health: food and drugs (Box 182, Folder 27)
      - Health: insurance (Box 182, Folder 28)
      - Health: Medicare (Box 182, Folder 29)
      - Health: smoking (Box 182, Folder 30)
      - Housing (Box 182, Folder 31)
      - Human services: general (Box 182, Folder 32)
      - Human services: Social Security (Box 182, Folder 33)
      - International relations: general (Box 182, Folder 34)
      - International relations: Central America (Box 182, Folder 35)
      - International relations: human rights - general (Box 182, Folder 36)
      - International relations: Jewish human rights [empty when transferred] (Box 182, Folder 37)
      - International relations: Middle East (Box 182, Folder 38)
      - International relations: hunger (Box 182, Folder 39)
      - International relations: trade (Box 182, Folder 40)
      - Judicial: general (Box 182, Folder 41)
      - Judicial: abortion (Box 182, Folder 42)
      - Judicial: civil rights (Box 182, Folder 43)
      - Judicial: crime (Box 182, Folder 44)
      - Judicial: gun control (Box 182, Folder 45)
      - Judicial: immigration (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Labor: general (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Labor: wages / pensions (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Newsletters (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Political: general (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Political: campaign reform (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Postal service (Box 183, Folder 7)
      - Public works [No material filed] (Box 183, Folder 8)
        No material filed this folder